ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影译站地址http://sysub.vip
■
我们又一次在
Well that was another great meal
全星球最棒的刺猬主题免下车餐厅
at the best hedgehog-inspired drive-in restaurant
■
翻译：  Silver银砸 雪莱 kyle
ShinY
深影
享用了美好的一餐 音速小子
on the motherfucking planet. Sonic!
即便是我这个最爱抱怨的人
Even I, the grouchiest shit of the bunch,
ShinY
深影
也无法拒绝他们的超大号德州烤芝士三明治
can't resist the oversized Texas toast grilled cheese
■
校对：  阿谚     后期： 孤亦
和酸橙汽水
and a limeade.
没有什么能比滑着轮滑送
There's nothing sexier than a chili dog
辣味热狗更性感了
delivered on roller skates.
而且我们说这些可没有收过钱
And we aren't even being paid to say this.
音速小子永远的神
Sonic just fucking rules.
贝尼是不是个乖宝宝呀
Who's a good Benny dog?
凯文 我还以为你住在
Kevin! I thought you were living in an apartment
好市多超市隔壁的公寓呢
by the Costco store.
ShinY
深影
嗨 外星人们
Hey, Solars.
是的 我从柯克兰村搬回来了
Yeah, I moved out of Kirkland's Signature Village
因为我跟妻子和好了
because the wife and I got back together.
对哦 我就说我好像听见有轻微的碰撞声
Yeah, I thought I heard some gentle humps
和湿漉漉的吮吸声从你卧房传出来
and wet slurps poppin' from your bedroom window.
哦 是的 我这几周一直在跟我老婆颠鸾倒凤
Oh, yeah, I've been stirring pussy for weeks.
ShinY
深影
这都要感谢我们的小狼贝尼
And it's all thanks to Benedog Cumberwolf here.
ShinY
深影
这个生物促成了你们的性交
This creature has facilitated your coitus?
他是只可卡贵宾犬
He's a cockadoodle.
一半可卡犬 一半贵宾犬
Half cocker spaniel, half poodle,
专门培育用来拯救婚姻
specifically bred to save marriages.
每当我要骂我的妻子时 他都能嗅到
He can smell when I'm about to disrespect my wife.
这很管用 因为她是个蠢...
It works because she's such a dumb bi...
好孩子
Good boy.
我们不是一直在寻找
You know how we've been trying to find something
可以让我们的家庭更完整的东西吗
that will complete us as a family.
这就是本季的主题
It's the theme of the season.
也许我可以像凯文一样
Perhaps we should
买一只开市客的宠物养
get a Costco pet like Kevin.
美国最大的连锁会员制超市
蛹宝宝不是宠物吗
Isn't the Pupa a pet?
比起宠物 他更像是小孩
He's more toddler than pet.
看 他正在看周六早间的动画片呢
Look, he's watching Saturday morning cartoons right now
就像小宝宝一样
like a wee baby.
蛹宝宝从来没有舔过我的脸
The Pupa's never licked my face,
但所有好的宠物都会舔主人的脸
which is something that all good pets do to their owners.
如果要养宠物 它一定要会舔我的脸
If we get a pet, it needs to lick my face.
我们不能养狗 它们爱打小报告
Well, we can't get a dog. They're narcs.
他们跟警察是一伙的
They work for the police.
那我们就养狗的死对头
Then we'll get the Bane to the dog's Batman.
猫咪
A cat.
你确定这是个好主意吗
Are you sure that's a good idea?
你难道没看过《家有阿福》
What about the whole Alf thing?
注: 剧中的外星人阿福天天都想吃掉住家养的猫咪
外星人不是会吃猫吗
Don't aliens eat cats?
那都是好莱坞左派编造出来的刻板印象
That's an offensive stereotype perpetuated by Hollywood liberals.
我们《外星也难民》绝对不会吃猫
The Solar Opposites would never eat a cat.
那我们先在就去买只猫来养吧
Then let's go get a pet cat right now.
它会成为我们家新的一员
It'll be a purr-manent part of the family.
该死的 我们真的跟阿福一样！
Goddammit, we are like Alf!
失乐普星球曾是一个完美的乌托邦
Planet Shlorp was a perfect utopia
可被小行星撞了个稀巴烂
until the asteroid hit.
一百多名成年人以及
One hundred adults and
他们的复制人带着发配的蛹宝宝
their replicants were issued a Pupa
逃向了... 外太空
and escaped into the... space,
奔走于杳无人迹的外星球 只为寻找新的家园
searching for new homes on uninhabited worlds.
我们迫降在地球
We crashed on Earth,
困在了这个本就人口过剩的星球上
stranding us on an already overpopulated planet.
没错 我就是个不停叨叨的话唠
That's right, I've been talking this whole time.
那个抱着蛹宝宝的就是我
I'm the one holding the Pupa.
我叫科沃 我是这剧的主人
My name is Korvo. This is my show.
蛹宝宝刚溜掉了
Bollocks, I just dropped the Pupa.
简直荒诞无稽 我痛恨地球
Ugh. This is ridiculous. I hate Earth.
这简直是人间地狱啊
It's a horrible home.
这里的人既愚蠢又令人困惑
People are stupid and confusing.
为什么他们那么容易缺水啊
Why do they dehydrate so easily?
哦 你心情不好
Oh, you're in a bad mood
是因为你没有喝够水
because you didn't drink enough water?
你干脆直接睡在水缸里得了 垃圾
Just sleep in a bowl of water, you pussy.
外星也难民
第四季 第四集
该死
Fuck.
我居然吃了二十二只猫和一只沙鼠
I can't believe we ate 22 cats and a gerbil.
是啊 这些沙鼠他们绝对卖贵了
Yeah, they really upsell you on the gerbils.
我们得找些不会勾起我们食欲的宠物
We need to think of pets we won't be tempted to eat.
所以不能要有毛 或者有猫内脏的
So obviously nothing with fur or cat organs.
我们需要的是 没有可爱到会让我们想吃掉
We need something that's not so cute that we want to eat it
但又有点可爱 还会舔我们脸的宠物
but is still sorta cute and will lick our faces.
会舔脸对我来说至关重要
Getting face licked is a real priority for me.
哒吧 呀吧 呀吧
Dabba yabba yabba.
确实 哒吧 呀吧 呀吧
Dabba yabba yabba indeed.
拼音竞赛
即拼字竞赛的
反转版
詹姆斯·厄尔琼斯高中
贾克森 你要发音的单词是 L-i-u
Jaxson, your word to pronounce is A-L-U-M-I-N-U-M.
拼音竞赛
你能用它造个句吗
Can you use it in a sentence?
不行 因为那样我就把词念出来了
No, because then I'd be pronouncing it.
休想糊弄我
Nice fucking try.
琉
Aluminork?
错误
贾克森 你个白痴
Jaxson, you idiot.
错得离谱
That was so wrong.
杰西 把这题答对你就能进地区赛了
Jesse, get this right and you're going to regionals.
你的单词是 X-i
Your word is W-A-T-E--
西瓜
Watermelon!
抢答零分
No points for early guessing.
但是对了
But that's correct.
我要我妈妈
I want my mom.
科沃       泰里      洋洋乐
听好了 外星人
Listen up, Opposites.
地区赛将会是你遇到的最艰难的比赛
Regionals will be your toughest competition yet.
你要跟费城的冠军们对决
You'll be up against the winners from Philadelphia.
费城出身的人
People from Philly famously have
以全国最标准的发音而闻名
the best pronunciation in the country.
拿着
Take these.
哇哦
Ooh.
这些是录音带吗
Wait, are these cassette tapes?
我以前好像在博物馆里看见过这个
I think I saw these in a museum once.
这东西音质不是很糟糕吗
Don't they sound terrible?
请把重心放在比赛上
Focus on the competition.
你没问题的
You'll do fine,
只要你有家人的支持
as long as your family has your back.
另外告诉你吧
And for your information,
音乐配上磁条的嘶嘶声才更好听
music sounds better with the hiss of a magnetic strip.
磁带的音色是无法被超越的
We will never beat the sound of a tape.
你想要我做什么
You want me to what?
帮我们做个恐龙
For you to make us a deeno-saur.
我们想要造个恐龙龙啦
We wanna make-a da deeno.
用辣酱造恐龙龙
Make-a da deeno with a-spicy a-sauce.
我们要恐龙龙 恐龙龙 恐龙龙
Make-a da deeno, make-a da deeno, make-a da deeno.
做个恐龙龙
make-a da deeno, make-a da deeno make-a da deeno!
闭嘴
Shut up.
你们为什么用劣质的马里奥口音讲话
Why are y'all talking in those janky Mario Brothers accents?
因为这很有趣啊
'Cause it's fun.
难道《外星也难民》就不能有个
Heaven forbid the Solar Opposites have
意大利辣肠的幽默吗
a pepperoni of fun for once.
听着 我不能创造有生命的物体
Look, I can't just make a living creature.
那如果用量子注射器呢
But what if you use the Quantum Injector?
你咋还凭空造词呢
You're just making words up now.
就是我们用来做趣味桶的那玩意儿
The thingy we used to make Funbucket.
对 那个玩意儿很靠谱
Yeah, that shit's canon.
噢 我把那给忘了
Ooh, I forgot about that.
你想要什么样的恐龙
So what kinda deeno-saur you want?
一点点汉娜和一点点芭芭拉
A pinch of Hanna and a dash of Barbera.
它必须会无条件舔我的脸
It has to lick my face, no exceptions.
而且必须足够聪明能懂我们的笑话
And it should be clever and get our jokes.
在我们笑的时候它也会笑
And laugh when we laugh.
并且它应该总是知道照相机在哪里
And it should know where the camera is at all times
然后偶尔对它顽皮的眨眨眼
and give occasional sly winks to it.
往后站点然后看着我做 小蠢货们
Stand back and let me do my shit, you dummies.
耶 恐龙
Yay, deeno.
恐龙 恐龙 恐龙
Deeno, deeno, deeno.
这里什么情况啊
What the cheese and crackers is going on here?
那是谁
And who is that?
那是我们的新恐龙
That's our new deeno.
你们这些家伙居然不问问我就养个新宠物
You guys got a pet without asking me?
我们以为你在 呃
We assumed you'd, like,
掉进了下水道之类的什么东西
fallen in a sewer or something
忙着解决什么事情 我不知道 管道类的东西
and were dealing with, I don't know, sewer stuff.
我是去参加了拼音比赛
I was competing at the Pronunciation Bee,
你们这些家伙说会来看的
which you guys said you'd come watch.
舔杰西的脸 舔它 快 现在
Lick Jesse's face. Lick it, lick now.
呃 我现在可没有时间
Ugh. I don't have time for this.
我得去为地区赛做准备
I have to get ready for regionals.
再问一下 有多少个参赛地区来着 一千个吗
Again, how many regions are there? A thousand?
这只恐龙最好不要打扰到我学习
This deeno better not interrupt my studying.
我敢保证这只恐龙会表现得
I'm sure the deeno will behave in a completely different way
和我们目前为止所看到的大不相同
than the only way we've seen him behave so far.
你看到那表情了吗 好孩子
You see that shit? Good boy.
蒲公英
Dandelion.
监护人
Chaperone.
光剑
Light saber.
屁股
Butt cheek.
你们能小点声吗
Would you please keep it down?
我们正在和小龙进行疯狂赛车比赛
We're doing madcap race car driving with the deeno.
看 我们连卑鄙的胡子都戴上了
Look, we even have our dastardly mustaches.
小龙要跑远了
The deeno's getting away.
跟着他进那条新隧道
Follow him into that brand new tunnel.
嘿
Hey.
救命
Help.
我要怎么恢复啊
How do I do the thumb thing?
伙计们 伙计们 快来啊
Guys? Guys, come on.
帮个忙
A little help.
地峡 洁食 松鼠
说实话 这些线根本没有帮到我学习
Honestly, the string doesn't help me study,
拼音练习
但它看上去不错
but it does look nice.
噢 这群傻蛋们 现在又在整啥活
Oh, cheese nuts. What is it now?
我们在解史酷比之谜
We're solving a Scooby-Doo mystery.
那个公园管理员说他知道时间
That park ranger said he knew the time,
但为什么他说时间
but why would he say time
除非他在时钟里
unless he's in the clock
这点我们之前都没有确认过
that we've never established before.
我猜你在想我为什么要费这么大的劲
I suppose you're wondering why I went through all this trouble.
闭嘴滚出去
Just get the fuck outta here.
一 二 一  二 三 四
One, two. A one, two, three, four.
小龙和外星人
♪ 小龙和它的外星人们♪
♪ The Deeno and the Opposites ♪
♪ 从史前时代到太空时代♪
♪ From prehistoric times to something space ♪
♪ 一些一些这个世界以外的东西♪
♪ Something something outta this world ♪
好了 好了 停下 停下
Okay, okay. Stop, stop.
仅仅是随心摇滚不起作用了
Just rocking from the heart isn't working.
我们需要去写一些歌词
We need to write some lyrics.
不不不 继续摇滚
No! Keep rocking.
小龙
Deeno.
你们昨晚练的唱歌
Your guys's band practice
毁掉了我的学习时间
ruined my study session last night,
现在我真的需要去临时抱佛脚了
and now I really have to cram.
我的录音带呢
Where are my tapes?
♪ 小龙和它的外星人们♪
♪ The Deeno and the Opposites ♪
你们覆盖掉了我的录音
You taped over my tapes?
为了获得唱片合约
We had to make a demo
我们恐龙乐队必须要制作一个样片
if we want to get a record deal
必须要制作一个样片
for our Deenosaur band.
洋洋乐看了'打倒男孩'的贝斯手的大师课
Yumyulack watched the bass player from Fall Out Boy's master class.
Fall Out Boy 打倒男孩 美国摇滚乐队
这些录音带是我唯一学石的途径
These tapes were the only way I had to starky,
我是说学习
I mean, uh, study.
噢 不 我发英已经不对了
Oh, no, I'm already mispronoons...
法音
mispra--
发英
mispro-- mis--
见鬼
Dammit!
杰西 你需要冷静下来 先坐下
Jesse, you need to chill out, sit down,
尝一个小龙做的墨西哥早餐玉米煎饼
and have one of these breakfast burritos the deeno made.
不过这会儿没有空椅子了
Though there aren't any chairs open now.
小龙坐的那张是你通常坐的
The deeno's sitting where you usually do.
而且 好像没有多的玉米煎饼了
Also, there's no more burritos.
他只为六个家庭成员做了六个煎饼
He only made six for the six members of the family.
小家伙
Little buddy.
猜猜谁把你给忘了
Guess who forgot about you!
让我们继续笑吧
Let's all resume laughing.
啊哦 杰西生气了
Uh-oh, Jesse's mad.
小龙 再舔一次她的脸
Deeno, give her another face lick.
不
No!
历史博物馆
我们有木乃伊！
嘿 古生物学家们 你们有时间吗
Hey, paleontologists, you got a minute?
噢 小姑娘 你一定是迷路了
Oh, little girl, you must be lost.
木乃伊展厅在另外一个大堂
The mummy exhibit is in the other hall.
其实我在找人来回答一些关于恐龙的问题
I'm actually looking for someone to answer some deeno questions.
真的吗
Really?
现在的孩子通常不怎么关心恐龙了
Kids usually don't care much about dinosaurs these days.
他们都痴迷于古埃及文化
They're all obsessed with ancient Egypt.
"我可以把这个象形文字发抖音吗"
"Can I TikTok this hieroglyph?"
"我可以把这个石棺分享到朋友圈吗"
"Can I WhatsApp this sarcophagi?"
让我感到恶心
Makes me sick.
恐龙们是那么酷
Dinosaurs are so cool.
天啊 我可太爱这些骨头了
God, how I love these bones.
现在全是那些假自拍
Now it's all about thirst trap selfies
和伊姆霍特普
with fucking Imhotep.
注: 埃及的一位神祇 也是一位真实存在过的历史人物
我们可以为你做些什么
What can we do for you?
好吧 我其实来自好莱坞
Well, I'm actually from Hollywood.
我们正在筹备一个故事
We're working on a story
需要了解一下如何才能在不惊动他人的情况下
and need to know how could someone get rid
把一头令人厌烦的恐龙赶出去
of an annoying deenosaur without anyone knowing?
你可以找一只别的恐龙把它吃掉
Mm, you could always get another dinosaur to eat it.
这好像没办法
That's not gonna work.
除了更大体型的恐龙 唯一强大到
Well, the only thing that was strong enough
可以杀死恐龙的东西恐怕只有
to kill the dinosaurs other than bigger dinosaurs
毁灭恐龙世界的那颗小行星了
was the asteroid that destroyed their world.
那就是我 需 要 的
That is exactly what I require.
见鬼 那女孩是懂拼音的
Damn, that girl can pronounce.
再见了 你这个该死的侏罗纪产物
Sayonara, you Jurassic fuck.
我怎么会让事情发展到如此失控
How have I let things get so out of control
我居然准备用小行星来谋杀一只小恐龙
that I'm about to do a murder on the deeno with an asteroid?
这不是我 我很抱歉 小家伙
This isn't me. I'm sorry, little guy.
事实是 我这么努力练习
The truth is, the only reason I tried so hard
准备拼音大赛是为了
with the Pronunciation Bee
让我的家人喜欢我
is to make the family like me.
现在感觉你好像取代了我
And it felt like you were replacing me,
但你只是一个友善的小龙
but you're just a friendly deeno pup.
好好享用专属大肋排吧
Enjoy your cartoonishly large ribs.
太蠢了 你这个贱人
Bad move, you stupid bitch.
小龙 你会说话
Deeno, you can talk?
我本来就会说话 而且你猜对了
I've been able to talk this whole time, and you were right.
我就是要取代你在家里的位置
I was trying to replace you in the family.
糟了
Oh, crap.
爱莎创造我时
When AISHA made me,
汉娜简直是友爱甜心的代名词
the Hanna was all the sweet friendliness.
不应该受到
She never should've tainted it
邪恶芭芭拉的污染
with the malevolence of Barbera.
所以你一直在装善良
You've been faking being nice?
这个计划已经酝酿六千五百万年了
This plan's been 65 million years in the making.
欢迎来到地球 蠢蛋
Welcome to Earth, shit bag.
来比剑啊 智障
Sword time, motherfucker.
泰里 你在干嘛
Terry, what are you doing?
我要干掉小龙
I was coming to kill the deeno
因为我觉得它会取代我在家里的位置
because I thought he was replacing me in the family.
什么 不可能 我也是这么想的
What, no way, I did too.
- 去死 去死 - 科沃
- Die, die, die. - Korvo?
你又在干嘛
Now what are you doing here?
我绝对没有打算用节庆道具
Uh, definitely not getting ready to smash the deeno
捶死小龙
with the holiday hammer because I thought
因为我觉得它会取代我
he was replacing me in the family.
绝了 我也是
Hey, that's how I was feeling too.
我们都嫉妒小龙 跟一家人一样
We were all jealous of the deeno, as a family.
这表示我们彼此相爱而且
That means we all love each other and...
蛹宝宝
Pupa?
你要给小龙吃美味辣酱吗
Are you bringing Deeno a nice bowl of chili?
你有病啊 蛹宝宝
What the shit, Pupa?
你这个小叛徒
You little traitor.
你能不能有点羞耻心
Would you grow some self-doubt, Pupa?
等一下
Wait a second.
这里面都是玻璃渣
It's full of broken glass.
蛹宝宝也想杀了小龙
The Pupa was trying to kill the deeno, too.
这就对了
There we go.
这算什么 你们这群智障
It doesn't matter, you stupid twats.
我受够你们这群外星人了
I'm sick of all your alien bullshit.
地球就该属于地球生灵
Earth belongs to earthlings.
恐龙已经灭绝了
Your whole species is extinct.
你只是外星科技创造的假货
We made you with alien science.
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
这次 小行星会和恐龙一起
This time, the asteroid's gonna help the dinosaurs
杀光你们
by killing you
小家伙和我会独占这座房子
so Little Buddy and I can have the house all to ourselves.
小家伙和你是一伙的
You and Little Buddy have teamed up?
是啊 小家伙
Yeah, buddy.
真扯淡
That is so fucked.
杰西 拼拼这个
Jesse, pronounce this.
S-i 死
D-I-E.
邻居们
Hey, neighbors.
抱歉大半夜的到你们后院
Sorry to walk in your backyard in the middle of night.
但我想...
But I was wondering...
- 好乖乖 - 快跑
- Good boy. - Run!
那是什么枪
How does that gun even work?
小行星又是从哪来的
Where are all these asteroids coming from?
光线把空间站变成香烟时
I was sure we were dead after that beam turned
我以为我们死定了
our space station into cigarettes,
幸运的是 我们还有支撑我们存活的
but luckily we had one thing we needed to stay alive.
希望
Hope.
没想到我们都讨厌恐龙
I can't believe we all hated the deeno.
我还以为你们都喜欢它
I really thought you guys loved him.
我以为养宠物能让我们团结
I assumed having a pet would bring us together,
结果我们需要的是共同的敌人
when what we really needed was something we all hated.
你们什么时候这么想的
When did you guys turn on the deeno?
自它从机器里蹦出来的时候
I knew as soon as he popped out of the machine.
只是我的剑还没发货
I was just waiting for my sword to come in from West Elm.
怎么才能阻止恐龙
So how should we stop-a da deeno?
我知道了
I've got it.
所有人坐稳了
Everyone hang on to your Tuts.
什么
What?
别躲了 小外星人
Come out, come out, little aliens.
我的视线会捕捉动作
My sight is based on movement,
我要你们全都跳着
and I wanna see you fuckers dance.
没事
Oh, it's okay.
这只是展品
That's just part of the exhibit.
可不是哦
Well, this isn't.
你被捕了
You're trapped.
杰西
Come on, Jesse.
我跟小家伙要把你的房间
Little Buddy and I are gonna turn your room
变成雪茄室
into a cigar lounge.
- 不可以 - 那我们的呢
- No. - What about our room?
撸管室
That'll be our jerk-off zone.
我就说那里很适合撸管吧
I told you that space would make a great jerk-off zone.
你觉得每个房间都适合
You say that about every room.
看来你弹尽粮绝了
Looks like you're fresh out of asteroids.
没事 我照样可以吃了你
Oh, no problem. I'll just eat you.
可以试试 但你吃素
Nice try, but you're a herbivore.
该死的 我真聪明
Fuck, I'm all smart.
泰里 我们就是植物
Terry, we're plants.
什么 我们是吗
Wait, we are?
你觉得这就吓到我了吗
Is that supposed to scare me?
我们之所以来这
The only reason we're here
就是因为我记得
is because I remembered
有人超爱恐龙骨头
who loves deeno bones more than anything.
谁在那 快出来
Who is that? Show yourself.
她说得对
Oh. Mm, the girl is right.
我们超爱恐龙骨头
We love dinosaur bones.
但之前只有干巴巴的化石
But they're always so dry and fossilized.
你有血淋淋的骨头了
You've got wet bones.
古生物学家 退后
Paleontologists. Stay back!
等等 停下 我可是活生生的恐龙
Wait, wait, stop. I'm a living dinosaur.
你们可以观察我的行为
Observe me. Learn from my behaviors.
我们可以合作
We-- we can work together.
如果我们想研究活生生的东西
If we wanted to study living things,
不就去当动物学家了吗
we would've been zoologists.
血淋淋的骨头
Wet bones. Wet bones.
- 血淋淋的骨头 - 骨头
- Wet bones. - Bones!
大家冷静
Everyone, be cool.
不要激怒他们
Don't do anything to piss them off.
我们能做到的
We've got this.
看 埃及展品
Oh, an Egypt exhibit.
快跑
Run!
你能拿冠军 我很骄傲
I'm so proud that you took first prize.
光（恭）洗（喜）
你拼音可真厉害
You pronounced the hell out of that shiz.
这就对了
There it goes.
谢谢大家
Aw, thanks, guys.
真高兴大家能团结在一起
I'm just glad we were all there together.
这就是家庭的意义
That's what family is for.
来 我们抱在一起
Now let us clutch each other in a manner
感受我们的爱
that demonstrates affection.
你走开
Hey, you can't be part of the hug.
你是跟恐龙一伙的
You teamed up with the deeno.
小家伙
Little Buddy?
不要假装什么都没有发生过
Don't pretend like it never happened.
我们知道该怎样处理你
We know exactly what to do with you.
爱莎 准备好冷冻舱
AISHA, prepare the cryo pod.
我们要把小人发射到太空
We're launching Little Buddy into space.
- 冷冻舱已经没有了 笨蛋- 你说什么
- The cryo pod's gone, dummy. - Fucking what?
你忘了吗 你曾经用它把那家伙发射到了太空
Remember, you used it to shoot that guy into space.
全水晶骨骼伏特加子弹
That whole crystal skull vodka bullet thing?
我 我想我回忆起了一些事情
I, I think I remember something about that.
胡扯 我猜我们只需要把它扔到
Crap. Well, I guess we'll just toss Little Buddy
垃圾处理器中
down the garbage disposal.
那个家伙的名字叫什么来着
What was that guy's name?
我们发射到太空中的那个
That we shot into space?
管他呢 反正我们不会再看到他了
Who cares. We'll never see him again.
小家伙
Little Buddy?
银河警察
非X星球
暴风雨就要来了 是时候离开了
Looks like an incoming storm. Time to clear out.
但嫌犯怎么办
But what about the suspect?
什么 那个人类 已经三天了
What, the human? It's been three days.
在野外他肯定是无法存活的
There's no way he survived out there in the wild.
这个案子已经结案了
This case is closed.
第三天
Day three.
最后一批银河警察离开了这个星球
The last of the Silvercops have left the planet.
只剩下我一个人
I'm here all alone.
好冷 我饥肠辘辘
It's cold, I'm hungry,
而且我已经穿着我的第四套树叶内裤了
and I'm already on my fourth pair of leaf underwear.
我非常害怕 而且我非常想你 宝贝
I'm scared, and I miss you so much, baby.
我希望我现在就在你的体内
I wish I was inside you right now.
我爱你 本田S2000
I love you, Honda S2000.
我可牺牲一切
I would do anything to run my hands
只为了可以抚摸你的人造皮内饰
over your faux leather interior
听《速度与激情》的原声大碟
and listen to the Fast and Furious soundtrack
不顾一切地穿梭在高峰时段的车流中
while recklessly weaving through rush hour traffic.
太饿了
So hungry.
如果我可以抓到飞鱼就好了
If only I could reach the flying fish.
怎么回事
What the fuck?
看上去像是魔鬼云
That looks like an evil cloud.
它就是魔鬼云
It is an evil cloud.
该死 该死 该死
Shit, shit, shit!
哦 这就像速九中的画面
Oh, this is just like that part in Hobbs and Shaw.
等等 不 不
Wait, no, no.
等等 在《速度与激情》的哪部电影中
Wait, which of the Fast and Furious movies
有释放毒气的场景
was the one where they were gonna unleash the gas?
是速五吗
Was that Fast Five?
这果实
The fruit.
起作用了 这颗果实救了我的命
It worked. This fruit saved my life.
它的味道就像是索尼克的芒果泥
Plus it tastes like a mango slush from Sonic.
嘿 多谢提示 小兄弟
Hey, thanks for the tip, little bro.
太空猴子粪便
Space monkey shit.
第四晚
Night four.
或者第五第十晚或者我不知道
Or five or ten or I don't know.
自从那些银河混蛋试图陷害我
Ever since those silver fucks tried to frame me,
唯一发生的好事情是
the only good thing that's happened
每天早上我都能吃掉那些
is realizing I can eat the alien leech
吸附在我阴囊上的外星蚂蟥
I find attached to my scrotum every morning.
真是奇怪我的第一反应竟然是吃掉它 但是
Definitely weird my first instinct was to eat this, but
它真的美味
it's worked out.
哦 嘿 小家伙
Oh, hey there, little fella.
哦
Oh.
很高兴第一次看到一些友善的面孔
Nice to see some friendly faces for once.
你们真是一群小可爱
Aren't you a bunch of little cuties.
啊
Ow!
正当我想情况不会再糟糕的时候
Just when I thought it couldn't get any worse,
我正在失去两个脚趾头
I'm now missing two toes,
并且正躲在一株恶心的的外星树上
and hiding in a gross alien tree.
这是我人生的谷底
This is my rock bottom.
这是我的《速度与激情2》
This is my 2 Fast 2 Furious.
原来是这种感觉
So that's what that feels like.
没有比这更糟的了
Doesn't get any worse than that.
哦 妈的
Oh, shit!
妈的 妈的 妈的
Shit, shit, shit.
真是倒霉
Fuck me.
这里是个坟墓
This thing's a tomb.
混蛋
Fuck you.
我不能再这样了
I can't do this anymore.
情况真是太糟了
It's too fucking much!
我的手表 我的汽车
My watch, my car.
我只想把这事做个了断而且死了算了
I just wanna get it over with and die.
嘿 伙计 鼓起勇气
Yo, bro. It's time to sack up.
唐老大
Dom Toretto?
格伦 你想要像个泼妇一样
Glen, are you gonna die in here
哭死在这吗
crying like a little bitch
还是想要击败那个怪兽呢
or you gonna go fight that creature?
我无能为力 那是只会飞的鲨鱼
There's nothing I can do. That's a sky shark.
我只是一个可怜的陆地人
I'm a pathetic ground human.
记不记得《速度与激情13: 亚特兰蒂斯之旅》中
Don't you remember what I learned in Fast and Furious 13:
我所学到的东西
Race to Atlantis?
家人 格伦
Familia, Glen.
家人不仅仅要在你的心中
Familia's inside you.
而且也要表现出来
But also outside.
当然 你可以忘记你的家人
And sure, you can forget about familia,
但是家人不会忘记你
but familia ain't forgetting about you.
好的 但那些都是什么意思
Okay, but what does any of that mean?
就是走出去驾车与那只鲨鱼战斗
Just go out there and use a car to fight that shark.
呜 呜
Vroom, vroom.
哔 哔
Beep beep.
♪ 速度与激情 ♪
Fast and the Furious
♪ 规则 一 ♪
Ja Rule, 01
♪ 这是我们的世界 ♪
Yeah, yeah, it's our world
♪ 请相信你们都不是真的 ♪
Please believe y'all ain't real
♪ 请相信 这是谋杀 ♪
Please believe, it's murder
家人
Familia!
♪ 加油 什么打动了我 ♪
Come on, what's touching me?
♪ 规则喜欢我或憎恨我 宝贝 ♪
R-U-L-E Love me or hate me, baby
♪ 三点三十六 宝贝 ♪
Refer to 3:36, baby
♪ 这就是规则 ♪
That's the rule
♪ 玩家 不要迷茫 ♪
Please, player, don't get it confused
♪ 看看我们现在玩的游戏 你们注定会输 ♪
See this game that we playing, y'all playing to lose
去死吧 飞天鲨鱼
Fuck you, sky shark.
♪ 规则 宝贝 ♪
Rule, baby
♪ 我最近失去了控制 ♪
I've been really outta control lately
♪ 让我听到你说耶耶耶 ♪
Let me hear ya say yea-yaay yea-yaay
♪ 狂野时刻  又一次在我赛道上急转弯 ♪
Wild time and again y'all swerve in my lane
♪ 我要拉起且让你的大脑爆裂 ♪
I'll pull up and start popping ya brain
♪ 你们都知道的名字 ♪
Y'all knowin' these broads names
♪ 奢华的香槟 ♪
Extravagant champagne
我为你骄傲 格伦
I'm proud of you, Glen.
你被暴揍
You got the shit kicked out of you.
但至少你尝试过了
But at least you tried.
多谢 唐老大
Thanks, Toretto.
家人
Familia.
♪ 你们都无法感觉到他 ♪
Y'all ain't feeling who?
♪ 你们都不喜欢他 ♪
Y'all don't like who?
讨厌这个星球
Hate this planet.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 sybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现